Mr. Chairman is here.
Welcome.
Congratulations, sir.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Hello.
- Congratulations, sir. - Congratulations, sir.
The founder of Soonyang.
It's him. Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
This is a dream. It can't be reality.
He died 20 years ago.
How could this be?
Do Jun.
Forgive me, Father.
Do Jun. You must watch your manners when you're around Grandfather.
He's young. It happens when you're overwhelmed.
I'll watch Do Jun. You can go on ahead.
Okay, then.
You sweet boy.
That's what your grandfather is like.
Nothing about his life is fun.
Would thorns break out on his hand...
if he were to just stroke your head?
Do Jun. Come with Grandma.
- "Grandma?" - Yes, sweetie.
Who...
Who am I?
You're so silly.
What kind of question is that? You are Jin Do Jun,
the youngest grandchild of the Soonyang family.
(The 24th Trade Day Business Medal Reward Ceremony)
It's the year 1987?
I'm a member of Chairman Jin Yang Cheol's family?
The youngest?
This can't be.
(The 24th Seoul Olympic Games)
(Reborn Rich)
(Episode 2)
Hyeong Jun, Do Jun, it's your first visit, isn't it?
This is Grandpa's place.
Whoa. Is this the main entrance?
It's massive.
It's just the same.
Jeongsimjae, the Soonyang residence that was theirs for generations.
A monk well-versed in geomancy...
picked out the auspicious spot for a home and told Chairman Jin...
as long as they were good at heart, money would never dry up.
The name "Jeongsimjae..."
literally means "rightful heart."
Wow, this is amazing.
One, two, three, four, five.
Gosh. How many rooms are there?
Thirteen.
What? How do you know that?
Have you been here without me?
Don't be silly.
Hyeong Jun, you promised Mom.
That you'll be a good boy today.
Yes.
Do Jun, you too.
Don't get too nervous.
It looks like you're nervous.
What?
Let's go. Grandma and Grandpa will be waiting.
Come along.
Bells toll and flowers are in bloom
Birds sing and people smile
I miss you, my love
Please do not leave my side
Where we first met and fell in love
The sweet roads I gave my heart to
In beautiful Seoul
I want to live in Seoul
However busy you are, the meat and fish cannot be cold.
Reheat and reserve every now and then.
- Do not scrimp on the salt. - I understand.
People these days eat less salt to stay healthy,
but food must be seasoned enough.
Don't worry about that, Mother.
Your first daughter-in-law has it under control.
I'll teach my sister-in-law how we do things.
Don't worry, okay?
My husband handpicked...
Soonyang Hotel's best cooks and waiting staff.
Don't worry about anything and stay by Father's side.
You're the guest of honour.
It's your father-in-law's birthday, and he's the one who won the medal.
How am I the guest of honour?
Don't say that.
Soonyang owes its immense growth to you, Mother.
Who doesn't know that?
That's such a sweet way of telling me to stop nagging...
and get out of the kitchen.
Hello, Hae In.
What should I do, Mother?
Don't you even think of doing anything.
Stay with Yoon Ki and the boys.
- Mother, leave it to us. - Okay.
Go on.
Do you want me...
- to prepare the fruit? - Mr. Ko, get the fruit.
Yes, ma'am.
They're gutsy.
He cut contact to marry a woman his parents disapproved of.
They then showed up after ten years...
to laugh and smile and enjoy having a family.
I'm incapable of putting on such an act.
She's not like us at all.
She was an actress.
She doesn't suit this family.
She belongs on stage.
Right?
Are you being bullies now because you weren't in school?
You have way too many wrinkles by your eyes.
- Ms. Ye Jun. - What are you doing?
When so many people are present?
Ms. Lee.
Don't try to play a daughter-in-law...
and stick to what you did.
Stand still like a portrait and smile prettily.
You're good at that.
Happy birthday, sir.
Let's have a drink.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday, sir.
He studied in Tokyo...
and works as a master at a sushi restaurant in Ginza.
The Japanese refused to let him go,
but I literally abducted him and got him...
on an early flight so he could cater to you today.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
I knew it.
Domestic goods still can't compare to Japanese.
How many?
Grains of rice. How many are there?
The ideal weight of fish and rice is 15g...
So how many?
- I apologize, sir. - There are 320.
A trained sushi master...
usually picks up 320 grains of rice to make one piece.
That many might be appropriate for lunch,
but on a day like this, or when served with alcohol,
use just 280 grains of rice, okay?
So it's not too filling.
I'll do that, sir.
Cheongwadae sent a messenger, sir.
- The Blue House? - Yes.
Sir.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
Thank you. Eat your fill.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Father. How did you know the number of rice grains?
Is there a Japanese restaurant in Soonyang Hotel, yes or no?
Of course...
There. Must I say more?
Hey, you.
Deputy CEO of Soonyang Electronics. Tell me.
What is this year's sales?
It's 2.3 billion dollars.
- Up by 15 percent... - And the Japanese?
H made 26.5 billion dollars, and T made 20 billion dollars.
Both more than ten times we did.
Our deputy CEO is right, then.
We still can't compare to the Japanese.
Is that true?
Still, we're number one in our country.
We never lost...
the top spot in Korea in the white goods market.
The top spot in Korea.
The top spot in Korea?
Are you competing in a national competition?
Father.
Yoon Ki wishes to say hello.
Congratulations on winning a medal and happy birthday, Father.
He opened a film distribution company.
His first movie will be shown this year.
Aren't you proud of him?
He did it all without your help.
He'll do well. He's your son.
He said he'll visit every weekend like the others.
If you permit it.
He did a great job raising both boys.
Hyeong Jun, Do Jun, come and meet your grandfather.
Bow.
Yes, Father.
Don't be so angry with him.
Do movies make money, mister?
Something more valuable than money...
Will it help Soonyang?
- Father. - It makes no money...
and won't help Soonyang.
Why are you my son?
- Honey. - Guests are leaving.
Throw salt after them.
It really is a party.
There are beggars everywhere.
He doesn't mean what he says.
Yoon Ki, you know what your father's like.
Don't take it to heart, okay?
Yes. Leave it at that today.
Let's take it slowly.
Let's go and eat.
You eat lots.
He married against his parents' will,
so 4-0's right to succession was revoked.
Hello.
That's exactly what I know.
But...
I'm missing.
I know all there is to know about Soonyang's Jin family.
But...
(Late Jin Yang Cheol, Late Lee Pil Ok)
(Jin Yoon Ki, Lee Hae In, Jin Hyeong Jun)
I have no information on 4-2 Jin Do Jun.
Why...
is my mind blank when it comes to 4-2 Jin Do Jun?
Why is that?
You know, sir,
how the great 6.29 Declaration came to be.
It was all thanks to the President's concern and thoughtfulness.
History will record him...
as the father of democracy in our land.
Try the tea.
It smells lovely.
In the next administration,
shouldn't the average man take the lead role?
History is marching on,
and Soonyang should join the flow.
The President wishes to give you an opportunity.
Mr. Lee.
Yes, sir.
Were you aware?
This gentleman from the Blue House knew.
This medal you see here.
The payment is deferred.
He's here to collect.
So,
how much do you want for it?
Your window just won't open
I'll knock on it with the moonlight of love
Jeez...
Oh, my love
Open the window to let in the breeze
Shoot.
Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun?
It's obvious what movies make money.
- HongKongers shooting guns. - "A Better Tomorrow?"
- Or Americans going to war. - "Platoon."
So what kind of movie are you making?
It's about the French people praying.
It's called "Under the Sun of Satan."
I thought you wanted to make a movie, not build a hotel.
Do you want to make everyone fall asleep?
Dad! Do Jun is in trouble.
He's upstairs now.
You broke this vase. Okay, kiddo?
We're the only ones in this room right now.
No matter what you say, everyone will believe me.
Why? Because I'm the rightful heir to the throne,
and Grandpa will side with me no matter what.
Did you just scoff?
You were a real mess even when you were young.
What? Have you lost your mind?
Seong Jun!
- Hey. My gosh, are you all right? - What happened?
- Do you know how much this costs? - Are you okay?
Father absolutely treasures this porcelain vase.
It was him.
He broke it. He tried to run away, but I caught him.
- Oh, dear. - Do Jun.
Is that true?
Hold on. Yoon Ki.
This is making me very uncomfortable.
Are you implying that Seong Jun could be lying?
How could you accuse Seong Jun of lying...
He is lying.
What? What do you mean?
The vase...
He's the one who broke it.
He was trying to steal the chairman's belonging.
I caught him in the act.
He got flustered and tried to run away, but...
- Hey! - No!
- Seong Jun! - Do Jun.
- Are you all right? - What is going on?
- Father. - Seong Jun...
It wasn't me, Grandpa.
- I didn't break it. I swear... - Enough.
Shut your mouth.
This happened in 1987,
at the 60th birthday party for your grandfather,
former Chairman Jin.
Year 1987.
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
And his 60th birthday party.
You smashed the Goryeo celadon that he cherished...
and was scolded by him for the first time.
The smashed vase?
Seong Jun.
Do you know what you did wrong?
Come here.
Sit down.
You see, I don't care about this vase.
Seong Jun, you will continue my legacy...
and become the owner of Soonyang in the future.
Okay?
Everything you say...
and do...
could make or break ten thousand employees' livelihoods.
Even their families' livelihoods will depend on you.
Yet you can't even keep your emotions under control?
Acting up like this...
It wasn't an adequate quality...
"Isn't an adequate quality..."
isn't an adequate quality...
"in someone who will run a business that is Soonyang."
in someone who will run a business...
that is Soonyang.
What I read in his autobiography is unfolding before my eyes.
It was white porcelain.
My grandfather's vase that I broke.
It wasn't Goryeo celadon. It was a white porcelain vase.
Everything is happening...
exactly as I know it.
The past as I know it.
I'm in Korea in Year 1987.
Then...
If that's the case...
(Jeongsimjae)
(Three Way Restaurant)
That was a great meal. Let's go.
- Thank you. - Did you enjoy the food?
- Yes. - Get back safely.
Hyeon Min?
Mom.
(Ajin Motors)
- Hyeon Min! - You're here.
Dad!
Hi, Hyeon Min!
Lucky you, Hyeon Min! Daddy picked up fried chicken for you.
Who do you like more? Mommy or Daddy?
Mommy!
- I knew it! - I'll do better.
- Do you need a hand? - No, I'm good.
Come on. Let's have this fried chicken.
We found Do Jun.
We'll get there soon too.
Thank you, Mr. Oh.
Okay.
Do Jun is okay. You can put your worries to rest now.
Thank goodness.
Hello...
Are you here alone? Your parents aren't here with you?
Can I have one serving of gukbap?
Sure. You can take that table over there.
Hello...
Do Jun.
What are you doing here?
I was so worried.
Get up. Let's go.
Let's go home.
Let's...
talk at home.
Okay?
(Daeil Bandage)
What's wrong, Do Jun?
What is it?
I'm relieved.
Mom's alive.
I'm so relieved.
Mom's relieved too.
Thank goodness...
I have you.
Don't cry.
That poor thing must've been so scared. Look how he ran away.
Well done.
Way to go.
Your son and grandsons came to see you after ten years.
How could you read a book after kicking them out like that?
My son and grandsons? Who?
I only scolded my eldest grandson,
Seong Jun. No one else.
You can't expect all your children to be the same.
Let at least one of them do what they want.
I fed them and paid for their education,
so I must get my money's worth.
I never invest in things where I can't get my money's worth.
You'd better not coddle Yoon Ki.
The others will turn out like him.
The only person in this family who I know nothing about...
is me, 4-2 Jin Do Jun.
Am I living as Jin Do Jun now because I'm possessed?
(Three Way Restaurant)
- Mom. - Hi, son!
Hey, you. Come here.
- Oh, look at you. - Gosh, stop!
- Run! Go! - Hey, where are you going?
- Oh, nice one. - Let's cheer for your brother!
- Nice. - Well done.
Or did I simply travel back in time?
If not that... Have I been reincarnated?
How did this happen?
(Daily Schedule, Timetable)
Why are you still up?
It's getting late.
Do Jun, what happened today... It must've been a lot for you.
At first,
I felt the same way.
"What am I doing here?"
"I don't belong in this world."
I couldn't understand them. It was very frustrating.
You felt the same way?
Does that mean...
It felt so foreign to me. I was scared,
and it was uncomfortable.
I almost regretted marrying your dad.
But now, it's not so bad.
I've found a reason to accept them as my family.
A reason to accept them as your family?
You and Hyeong Jun.
Do Jun.
I'm certain that you'll find your reason too, one day.
All the companies are dropping their prices for their 64K DRAMs.
Soonyang Semiconductor started exporting them this month.
Japan and the US are already dominating the market.
So if they're charging less than half of what we're asking for,
Soonyang Semiconductor will not survive in the market, sir.
What time is it now...
in New York?
It's 9pm, sir.
Is Im Pil Sung in New York now?
I'll tell him to give you a call at once.
No, don't wake him up.
Just tell him to fax it over when he wakes up.
- Fax? What do you need, sir? - His resignation letter.
Pardon me?
I didn't know that I had a knife held to my throat...
until I read that newspaper.
Do you think it's acceptable?
Did he go to the US to eat hamburgers?
I'm done paying for his hamburgers.
I saw the news, Father.
The American companies slashed their price from 3 to 1.80 dollars.
And the Japanese companies said they'd sell it for 0.30 dollars.
If we sell ours at the price the Japanese companies are offering,
we'll lose 130 million dollars this year alone.
We're like the shrimp...
getting squashed between two whales that are fighting.
The semiconductor business...
Let's just give up here.
I'm afraid we've come too far.
The initial investment alone...
Right, so let's cut our losses and call it quits.
Let's stop trying to fill the bottomless pit.
Youngjin Semiconductor has given up too.
They're being sold to a Japanese company.
Think of the question you always ask us.
Will the semiconductor business bring in money?
(Jeongsimjae)
What brings you by at this hour?
I'm sorry for causing you concern yesterday.
I'm here to apologize to Grandpa.
Look at you talking like a grown man. You're so mature.
Come with me. He's upstairs in his study.
Come on.
Kids should behave like kids.
Is she naive? Or is she becoming dense?
- Hey. - I'm talking about Mother.
Oh.
Isn't it so obvious?
Clearly, he memorized what his father told him to say.
He's talking like a man in his 40s.
Wait here.
He'll be out soon.
You can watch TV if you get bored.
- Okay. - All right, then.
("Two Kims Continue to Disagree on Single Candidacy")
("Last Minute Conflict Surrounding Single Candidacy")
You should deliver the campaign fund yourself...
and meet him in person.
What?
The general election will take place in April next year.
You need a nomination.
Oh, right. Honey, you know everything.
You sure take after Father.
I heard you had visitors from Cheongwadae yesterday.
Did they ask you to back Roh Tae Woo's campaign?
Mr. Lee only listens and never spills what he hears.
I'm your daughter, Father. Of course, I know that much.
You silly goose.
Take a seat.
You too.
Instead of calling you to Cheongwadae,
they came all the way here. It means the tables have turned.
It tells me that Roh Tae Woo is at a disadvantage.
I'm not surprised. After all the protests and uprisings...
to end the military dictatorship,
who'd want to vote for another Military Academy graduate?
Unless the entire nation is suffering from amnesia collectively.
The two Kims will agree on single candidacy soon.
The opposition power will win this time, Father.
That being said,
shouldn't you decide which candidate to support now?
Between DJ and YS, choose the one who's more likely to win...
Right. So who would that be?
DJ, obviously.
He is supported by all the student and civic groups...
that helped establish the direct election system.
Dong Ki, you should never get into politics.
We should support YS, not DJ.
I know DJ has many fans, but he also has many enemies.
When it's a neck-and-neck fight, the one with less enemies will win.
Aren't you saying that because you dislike DJ?
I heard Kim Dae Jung was against...
nominating Chang Je since he worked as a public security prosecutor.
Why are you roping Chang Je into this?
I am saying these things for the sake of the company's future.
- Father! - Be quiet.
I'm sorry for causing you concern, Father.
- Mr. Lee. - Yes, sir.
As for their approval ratings,
get Soonyang Economic Research Institute to look into it.
Tell them to find out which one of them deserves my money more.
Yes, sir.
Now, get out.
- Oh. - Hey, aren't you Yoon Ki's son?
I'm here to apologize to Grandpa for what happened yesterday.
Oh, my. Yoon Ki always had a sly side to him.
After not visiting us once for ten years,
he now sends his son here every day.
He came all the way here by himself because his parents told him to?
He sure takes after his father.
Good-looking and calculating.
Your youngest son's child is here to see you, sir.
I only have two sons. I didn't know I had another son!
I will talk to him and send him home, sir.
Come with us. Let's go downstairs.
Please tell Grandpa...
that I'm here to pay for the vase that broke yesterday.
That punk.
Hey! You little brat.
Hey, do you even know how much that vase costs?
Five bills?
It can't cost more than that.
Five bills? What? Five dollars?
Or 50 dollars?
No, five million dollars.
What? Five million?
Wouldn't that be enough to fund a presidential election campaign?
What? Presidential election campaign?
Please let Grandpa know.
If it were me, I'd back Roh Tae Woo's campaign.
Roh Tae Woo will become President.
Did you eavesdrop on the adults' conversation?
Clearly, your parents couldn't teach you any better.
Is this how your parents taught you?
No one teaches their children to be so brazen.
Just like how no one tells their children...
to steal their grandfather's things.
- Do Jun. - What?
Young Ki, you must be getting old.
He's just a kid. Why are you getting so worked up?
He's read some newspapers, so he's trying to sound like an adult.
Once DJ and YS agree on single candidacy,
Roh Tae Woo can't win.
I assure you that he won't win.
Single candidacy?
Do you think the two of them will actually reach an agreement?
I do not think so.
Now, that should be enough to compensate him for the broken vase.
I'll be off, then.
Goodness.
Oh, my. Yoon Ki did a great job, bringing up such a smart boy.
Oh, sorry.
Of course, it's nonsense.
So many people are rooting for single candidacy.
They won't betray the majority opinion.
Both YS and DJ...
have come this far because of their devotion...
to the democratization of the nation.
They won't gamble on their political careers.
Exactly.
Mr. Oh, take Mr. Chairman's grandson home.
Sir, there's breaking news about the presidential election.
You should see it.
What's the matter?
Kim Young Sam and Kim Dae Jung of the Democratic Party...
decided against single candidacy earlier today.
Kim Dae Jung clearly expressed...
that he was against the party convention,
which means they will both run for President.
Father.
Kim Young Sam and Kim Dae Jung met again...
- Father! - to negotiate the details...
regarding single candidacy but failed to reach an agreement.
Their talk ended when they decided...
to postpone the deadline to next Monday,
which is when Kim Dae Jung would have to reply by.
Wait, stop!
Mr. Chairman would like to speak with you.
Right now.
Tell me.
How did you know they'd decide against single candidacy?
I wouldn't be able to concede. That's why.
Because I'd get greedy.
When three candidates are running for class president,
the top two candidates will never join hands...
because they both believe that they will win.
Rather, they'll do whatever it takes to make each other lose.
They'll bad-mouth each other and fight.
Then their teachers and classmates...
will realize that they, in fact, don't deserve the position.
Just like that, they'll drag each other down.
So the one who was least likely to win will end up winning.
You mean he'll win by default.
Roh Tae Woo will become President, by default.
So I should back Roh Tae Woo. Is that right?
If I were you, I'd give him the money before he became number one.
A lot more than the amount he may be expecting.
He'll be grateful if you give it to him when he's still number three.
But if you wait until he becomes number one,
he'll take it for granted.
- Mr. Lee. - Yes, sir.
Tell Mr. Oh to have the car ready.
Yes, sir.
- Hey. - Mr. Oh, have the car ready.
Let me ask you one more question, then.
I believe I've already paid you for the broken vase, Grandpa.
It's nothing difficult. It's just a quiz.
Then there must be a prize for getting it right.
Because it's a quiz.
I don't like to do things for free either.
We talked about how number 3 can win by default because number 1 and 2...
are busy fighting, right?
But there's this saying too.
"The shrimp is squashed to death when two whales fight."
Then do you think there's a way...
for the shrimp to beat the whales?
You're just like other kids, after all.
Hey.
Come here.
How did you know...
the candidates won't be unified?
Yoon Ki, no.
Did your father tell you so?
My brother said so.
Your brother?
This is what we do in times like these.
"It's obvious at a single glance."
What's with this punk?
That's a buzzword by Hwang Ki Soon.
Hwang Ki...
You punk! That's not the way you should talk to your elders.
Do you think there's a way for a shrimp to win against a whale?
I guess you can't give up on the semiconductor, Chairman Jin.
Why do you think I'm so set on semiconductor?
Last summer, in Mokpo, Ulsan, and Changwon,
when the labourers of our factories put on headbands...
and stood there protesting...
with cranes and excavators, asking me for a raise...
and the formation of a labour union,
I only thought about this...
in my head.
I am done doing business by using labourers.
Then...
From now on,
we must do business with technologies to make a living.
Semiconductor is...
the future business of Soonyang.
I see.
Do you ask if it'll be worth any money?
Am I the only one who sees this?
Why is there nobody else who can think like this old man?
We have to make an astronomical investment,
but we do not know if it'll be a success.
The semiconductor business is nothing but a risk,
no, more like gambling at this point, Chairman Jin.
Once our finances look better...
by overseas construction business with the government's cooperation,
why don't you resume the semiconductor business then?
Do you know what democratization is?
I'm not sure.
Before, only a single soldier was after the money in my pocket.
That turned into three civilians.
That's democratization.
(Best Taste! Best Quality!)
Please give this to the president.
That I believe he will surely put an end...
to this era of military dictatorship.
Thank you.
(People's Hiking Club, 1987)
Our chairman was touched deeply by your character...
when you said you will not take any political retaliation.
Please use this...
for the sake of peace in Korea just as you wanted.
The campaign of Roh Tae Woo of Democratic Justice Party was...
held in the square in front of Gwangju Station.
As soon as the campaign began at 2pm,
young people and university students came out protesting...
and chanting Kim Dae Jung's name.
("Tear Gas Dropped During Roh Tae Woo's Speech")
(October 1987, "Business Weekly")
(Korea's Semiconductor in Crisis, Youngjin Semiconductor to Be Sold)
We talked about how number 3 can win by default because number 1 and 2...
are busy fighting, right?
Then do you think there's a way...
for the shrimp to beat the whales?
("Small Korean Businesses Sacrificed in This Global Chicken Game")
Small?
Snack time.
I finally realized...
the answer to Chairman Jin Yang Cheol's quiz.
Grandma, I have something I'd like to say to Grandpa.
Is he home right now?
He's on a business trip to Baghdad?
Then when will he return?
October 29th.
By any chance,
do you know what his flight number is?
Okay. Thank you, Grandma.
I'll call you again next time.
Bye.
CAL 828.
The CAL incident of 1987.
An aircraft with 95 passengers and 20 flight attendants...
went missing above Yangon, Myanmar.
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol will return to Seoul...
on that very plane, CAL 828.
At midnight in Korea, it will take off from Baghdad Airport,
in three hours.
I only have three hours of time...
to save Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
So they refuse to accept the terms we suggested?
If we press them by using the royal family, it can happen.
The royal family again?
The second son of the King, Prince Hussein,
plans on visiting Abu Dhabi...
on the same flight as us, CAL 828.
Mr. Lee right here is telling me to do a sales pitch...
even when I'm on my flight.
(Korea Telecom)
You have reached the customer service center.
It's a bombing attack. We must stop this terrorist attack.
A bombing attack?
On flight CAL 828 from Baghdad Airport to Seoul,
a North Korean agent will plant a bomb.
If you aren't prepared, it will blow up in open waters...
and kill two passengers.
Hey, kid.
A prank call on bombing attacks and abductions of an aircraft is...
a crime you will be punished for and will have to pay for damages...
- through a civil action. - It's not a prank. It's true.
Hundreds of lives are in danger.
You have to save them!
Hello?
Of course.
No one will be able to believe me.
And that I am from the future.
That I already know everything that will happen...
from now on.
(Korea Telecom)
It's even hard for me to believe everything that's happening now.
Grandma, open the door, please.
We have no time, Grandma!
Grandma!
- Bring him a blanket, please. - Yes.
Goodness, what brings you here at this hour?
Grandma, can you let me speak to Grandpa?
There is something I must tell him.
We have no time, Grandma.
Chairman Jin is in a meeting with local Iraqi staff.
I will pass on a message if you leave it with me.
Yes, I am ready.
I finally found out the answer to the quiz you asked, Grandpa.
A way for a shrimp to beat the whales.
Once you see this note, I believe that you will...
change your flight.
- Great work. - Great work.
Did anyone call from Seoul?
- No, nobody called. - Good.
Where is it?
Man, where did it go?
- Mr. Kim. - Yes!
- Did you lose something? - No!
Check if anything is missing before we go to the airport.
Yes, sir.
Great work, sir.
Where is this thing?
Thank you.
Next story. On October 6th, HHI-1200, embarked the equipment...
to build the Korean Research Center and left for Antarctica from Ulsan.
Yesterday night, I began to hate you
After 94 days, the ship stopped momentarily...
at Port Valparaiso, their last stopover.
- I began to hate you - Do Jun was watching it first.
- Darn it. - They will have arrived...
- by next month at the latest... - I'm watching the news right now!
on King George Island.
Jin Do Jun.
An aircraft with 95 passengers and 20 flight attendants...
went missing above Yangon, Myanmar.
The details of the accident is yet to be discovered.
Let us report to you...
the details we know so far along with the list of passengers.
Let us connect to the reporter.
Have you checked the list of passengers?
Young Ki is on it.
Yes, is that the final list of passengers...
from Baghdad Airport?
No, right?
Your father wouldn't pass away in such vain.
I'm... I'm sorry, Mother.
Oh no, Mother! Mother!
- Mother. - Mother! Oh no.
Water, bring her some water!
Goodness, Mother. You poor woman.
Chairman Jin's autobiography did not mention the CAL incident.
Then did something change...
because I came here?
Was I too late?
If I had remembered a little earlier,
could I have saved Chairman Jin?
Get it together!
- No! - No, Father!
Father!
Father.
- Father. - Father!
Did someone die around here?
Why are you all crying?
Father, I checked the final list of passengers from Baghdad just now.
So? Are you disappointed...
that I came back alive?
Don't say it like that, Father!
Because of you, we were all just...
Good grief. You were all worried for nothing.
Your father is yet to become a ghost.
Your mom's face is what looks like a ghost.
There was a change in his schedule due to business,
so he had to arrive in Seoul earlier.
We switched to another flight at the stopover, Abu Dhabi,
so we were able to avoid this disaster.
Great job.
- Father. - Father.
Father.
What a relief, Father.
I heard you suddenly had a business in Seoul.
I don't know whose business it is, but I'd like to go bow to them.
It's Youngjin Semiconductor.
They're selling the business, right?
I hear they will do it soon.
I bought it today.
Youngjin Semiconductor.
- What? - What?
Wait, weren't you going to give up on the semiconductor business?
Father, you're going to jump in on this fight of whales?
I'm going to make the shrimp bigger...
so that the shrimp won't die in a fight between whales.
- Father. - No matter how long it takes...
or how much I have to invest,
I will make this shrimp as big as a whale.
But Father, right now, it's not...
I just came back from my death.
Do you think there is anything I'll be afraid of?
(Pending Approval)
I finally found out the answer to the quiz you asked, Grandpa.
A way for a shrimp to beat the whales.
It's to make the shrimp bigger.
Then it won't die in the midst of a whales' fight.
If you do not give up, time will be on the shrimp's side.
The proposal of the buyout of Youngjin Semiconductor...
ends at 5pm on the 29th.
Once you see this note,
I believe that you will change your flight.
Chairman Jin.
Are we stopping over at Abu Dhabi?
Yes.
Find the earliest flight to Seoul.
Congratulations, Mr. President.
During your presidency,
please allow Soonyang to monopolize...
the semiconductor business.
Thank you.
Just as you said,
I handed over the fund for the presidential election myself.
Why did you...
tell me to fund...
the second and third runners who aren't going to make it?
Once the first place graduates,
there will come a day for the 2nd and 3rd to win.
By any chance,
do you know what the future holds?
You knew the single candidacy will fall under.
You knew Roh Tae Woo would be elected.
And...
(I finally found out the answer to the quiz you asked, Grandpa.)
you knew CAL 828 will blow up.
You knew everything.
Is that true?
Answer me!
I did know.
Not the future,
but I knew what was in your heart.
There is no way for a shrimp to win against whales.
You gave me that quiz...
trying to grasp for straws because you knew...
your new attempt seemed reckless.
You weren't looking for an answer.
You were looking for approval and support.
All I knew was...
how you felt in your heart.
Why is he seeing him alone in the study?
I mean, without Mr. Lee.
- What's with Father? - Tell me about it.
That rarely happens for us too.
Young Ki.
You got the answer,
so you deserve the prize.
How much do you want?
I don't need money.
Once I am old enough to use that money,
its monetary value would have dropped.
Is that so?
I'd like land.
A place with lots of plants and trees.
I like this area, right here.
That land was used to make pottery. It's useless.
(Map of Seoul)
(Gyeonggi Province, Seongnam, Bundang-dong)
Do you want the land in Bundang that badly?
Let's see.
How does 160,000m² sound?
There is one more thing I'd like, Grandpa.
I think I'm done paying you out.
Then let's make it a deal.
You need to have something that I do not have...
for a deal to be made.
Do you think there is anything I do not have?
Because you can't buy this with money.
I'll bring you something that the Soonyang family doesn't have.
The acceptance letter to the most prestigious college,
Seoul National University, School of Law.
You're right.
An acceptance letter, I cannot buy that.
Can you do this?
What can I give you in return?
Gather round, everyone.
Jeong Rae.
Yes, Father.
Starting with the family gathering this weekend,
make sure you set out...
enough utensils for Do Jun's family as well.
Why won't you answer me?
Every week?
Do Jun here is my grandson.
Do you understand now?
Family.
4-alpha was right.
There must be a reason why I became this family.
The reason why I became family with the Jins.
Right here.
One of these people...
killed me.
How do you feel about entering SNU's law program as the top?
Tell us your secret.
How did you get in as the top of the class?
- Say something. - Please introduce yourself.
Well.
I'm sure you all know my name.
So is this what you're looking for?
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol's grandson,
College of Law, the class of 1996. My name is Jin Do Jun.
I was born as Jin Do Jun...
not as spirit possession, time travelling,
or reincarnation.
This life is my opportunity.
(Reborn Rich)
Play. Have fun.
Go on group blind dates, regular blind dates,
casual dates, and go out with someone.
We've met before, right?
Did you meet her? When?
In 20 years' time.
Do Jun, you're back!
Why does Father play favourites with the youngest, Do Jun?
Do Jun has exchanged the money in the account into dollars.
I'd like to invest in companies in the US.
Never bet on things that you aren't sure about.
I have a lot of money, Mr. Oh.
There is a problem.
Just why?
It's a foreign investment company.
Mr. Chairman...
would like to pass Soonyang down to someone who is like him.
Do you simply have good discernment?
Or are you just lucky?